[theme music playing]
[tense music playing]
[screaming]
[shattering sound]
One million for Madrigal's body.
And another million for Diego's corpse.
[Ivy] Okay. We can't afford
to make any more mistakes.
I need a strong case against Emilia.
[Georgina] We need a whistleblower.
Divine Uytengco.
[Julio] I will make sure
our kingdom is still standing
when you wake up.
I will go against Diego Torillo.
I will run for governor.
My conscience keeps eating at me.
I'm ready to divulge
Ma'am Emilia's corrupt activities.
[Ivy] Jepoy and Diego's lives
are in danger.
Julio has issued a shoot-to-kill
order against them.
-[screams]
-[Jepoy firing shots]
Get down!
[gunshots]
[Ivy] What's happening? Mom!
You're a monster, Julio Ardiente!
-Camia Cruz!
-[shots fired]
[Diego grunting]
[Marlon] Diego!
[Julio] Make sure Diego Torillo
knows he was the target
of the shootout.
That way he'll know he's responsible
for what happened to his supporters.
-Who shot my mother?!
-Julio Ardiente.
Julio, you bastard.
Doctor, how's my mother doing?
[doctor] She had to undergo surgery, but…
we were able to revive her.
[Anna] Is she safe now?
[doctor] Yes, she's in the
recovery room right now.
We'll inform you when you can visit her.
All right, doc. Thank you very much.
[Loring] That Julio Ardiente
is nothing but a demon!
He even has the nerve to run for governor!
They're confident
because they think
the people still support them
despite the things they do.
But why did he attack now all of a sudden?
The Ardientes know.
They already know about what you did.
They suspect that
you and Jepoy shot Arnaldo,
and they attacked the headquarters
because you were one of their targets.
I'm sorry about what I said.
I just lost my temper.
I didn't mean any of it.
Cut the sweet talk, Raul.
I've already seen this before.
[sighs] Just tell it to me straight.
What do you need?
Do you need my money?
My power?
My body?
-Just say it.
-Someone met up with Emilia.
Another Jaguar like me.
If that's true,
then it can only mean one thing.
The real Jaguar is finally out of prison.
Are you Jaguar?
I am.
Your men told me that you're
the one who can help me avenge
my father's death.
You see, I have a feeling the Ardientes
were behind my father's murder.
I'll help you.
I have my men and my weapons.
And I have…
lots of money.
We'll get along, then.
And why should I trust you, Jaguar?
Because I want to acquire
the Ardiente gambling dens…
along with all their power.
I need someone who'll act
as Jaguar while I'm in prison
and manage my men while I'm gone.
I should've killed Julio
when I had the chance.
We can help each other, Raul.
Help me investigate my dad's death,
and… I'll give you everything you need.
[Raul] I decided to go with your deal.
[Natalie] So, who killed my father?
Emilia had the senator killed.
[Natalie screaming]
I'll kill her!
Right now, I'm in control
of the situation.
So, I can provide you
with everything you need.
But you have to give me what I need too.
I need to be stronger than the Ardientes.
You can tell Jaguar
that Raul finally agreed.
Don't worry, I will.
Then, just give it up!
Give Jaguar's mask and identity
back to him.
That's what I would do if I were you.
I can't give him back the mask.
Not until I've accomplished all my goals.
But first, I need Julio Ardiente's power.
Okay.
But…
you better hunt him down
before he hunts you down first.
I'll be ready for him.
I'll die before I hand over Jaguar's mask.
[tense music playing]
[exhales]
I've told you so many times,
but you still haven't changed.
Brother or not, I'll have you locked up
if that's what it takes
to set you straight.
Then you're a useless brother,
you bastard!
[tense music playing]
[woman] Nurse, please make sure
he lives, please.
[man] Doctor! Over here!
[man] Miss!
Diego.
Look at what they did to my mother.
They're monsters!
Why did this have to happen to us?
Why did they have to hurt my mother?
-Dear.
-Yes, Mom?
Dear!
It hurts!
Those bastards.
-Diego.
-All of them.
Stop it, Diego!
I said, stop it!
What's happening to you?!
Anna, you saw what happened to Aunt Camia.
The Ardientes were after me.
No one else should've gotten involved.
If it's me Julio wants,
they should shoot me, not them!
Wait, Diego.
I said, wait!
Don't stop me, Anna.
I'll go straight
to the Ardientes and face them
so no one else gets hurt.
They'll kill you, Diego!
And if you die, Lily will be all alone!
You'll leave us all alone!
The ones who care about you,
the ones who believe in you!
Don't blame yourself.
What the Ardientes did was not your fault!
So, don't go, Diego.
The people here need you.
Lily needs you.
-Ivy.
-Jepoy.
What happened? Did the Ardientes
try to kill you too?
They ambushed me too.
What about you?
I'm okay. But my mother…
and Diego were shot by the Ardientes' men.
The Ardientes attacked the headquarters.
Thankfully my mother
and Diego are safe now.
Jepoy, you need to be more careful…
because Julio has a
shoot-to-kill order against you.
The Ardientes know that
you're the one who shot Arnaldo.
Sorry, Ivy.
Where are you going?
To the Ardientes' place.
I was the one who shot Arnaldo anyway.
No.
-Ivy. Ivy, all this is my fault.
-Stay here.
No, it's not!
Yes, you did shoot Arnaldo.
But you only did it to save my life!
I owe you my life, Jepoy.
If you go to the Ardientes'
house, they will win.
And, after killing you,
who will they kill next?
They will also kill us.
You're not going anywhere. Stay here.
I know you can't wait
to go after the Ardientes.
The same goes for me, Jepoy!
But we need to stick to the plan.
Julio won't know what hit him.
[Diego] Miss Cora.
I think it would be
better if you hide for a while.
You're not safe here.
We'll just call you when we need you.
What's important now is your safety.
No matter how much
the Ardientes threaten me,
you still have my support.
Thank you.
Thank you, Diego.
Well, I better go.
Please take care.
You too.
Anna, if only I'd been more vigilant…
then I could've protected Aunt Camia.
Diego, you can't save everyone.
And it's not your fault.
It's enough for you
to teach them to be brave
and stand up for themselves.
[machine beeping]
[footsteps approaching]
[instrumental theme music playing]
Mom.
Mom, you're awake.
I'm so glad you're okay.
Mom, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for…
getting you involved in my vengeance
against the Ardientes.
I know…
I could've just taken you
far away from here
and lived a peaceful life instead.
But I'm sorry, Mom.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for choosing
to sacrifice myself.
But this isn't just for us, Mom.
This is for everyone who's ever
been abused by the Ardientes.
I promise I won't let them
hurt you anymore.
I promise.
["Wildflower" by Arnel Pineda playing]
♪ Let her cry ♪
♪ For she's a lady ♪
♪ Let her dream… ♪
I love you so much, Mom.
Thank you for always being by my side.
[sniffles]
♪ She's a free and gentle flower
Growing wild ♪
[suspenseful music playing]
[phone ringing]
Hello?
I'll be needing your help again.
It's time to take down
Emilia Ardiente next.
Hello, darling!
I've transferred 20 million
pesos to your account.
No more, no less! Woman of my word.
Thank you, Divine.
I know I can always count on you.
Of course. Just keep the money coming in!
[Emilia] Of course! Don't be silly.
There's always more where
that came from, you know?
[laughs] I'm sure.
I know I can count on you too.
[Divine] Okay! Gotta go! Bye!
[tires screeching]
[Divine] Thank you!
[Divine exclaims]
Who are you?! Who are you?!
[Divine exclaiming, wailing]
Someone, help me!
Help!
[cries] Please don't hurt me!
What do you plan to do with her?
[tense music playing]
Yes, Papa?
[Julio] It's a good thing
I caught up with you.
You have to hear the results
of our little investigation…
on the one who shot your son.
You know, we were able to trace
the gun that was used…
by the culprit.
Do you know who it's registered under?
Let me guess.
Ivy Aguas.
Nah.
No, no.
That would be too…
predictable.
It doesn't suit our story.
It's a plot twist
that no one would've expected.
Then, who owns it, Papa?
Surprise! Surprise!
The gun belongs to me.
What?!
How did it happen?
I was asking myself the same question
until I remembered…
how that gun was part of my armory…
that got raided by Jaguar.
Jaguar was the one
who tried to kill your son.
[dramatic music]
Boss, another Jaguar attacked us
and took over one of our gambling dens.
He called you a fake.
[man] Hold on, I'm confused.
Who's the real Jaguar, anyway?
You or him?
It doesn't matter who the real Jaguar is.
What matters now is your loyalty.
So, either side with me,
or that impostor.
Now,
whoever's on my side…
can stay here.
While those of you who aren't…
can leave.
Me, Boss.
I'm on your side.
What's up with you all?
Our boss has been helping us
all this time,
and now you doubt him?
Like I said, I'm on your side, Boss.
We don't know who that other guy is,
so if I were you, I'd choose to stay.
[man] Boss, we're on your side.
We won't let you down.
[phone ringing]
Hello, Jaguar.
We have to talk, and this time around…
you have no right to refuse.
This is important.
[tense music playing]
-Emilia.
-You animal!
How could you do this to me?!
You betrayed me!
Wait, Emilia. What are you talking about?
Don't play dumb with me!
I know you tried to kill my son!
My father traced the gun
that shot Arnaldo,
and this is what he found!
Take a look, traitor!
Hold on, Emilia.
So, don't you dare lie to me!
See for yourself!
What are you up really to, huh?!
I have no ill intentions toward your son
because he's not on my blacklist.
That's the gun I gave Madrigal,
but I didn't order him to shoot Arnaldo.
He probably did that for personal reasons.
I bet he wanted revenge on your family.
Then, prove it!
Kill Madrigal! Kill him!
I don't have to prove anything to you.
He's your henchman,
so he's your responsibility!
Kill him!
[tense music playing]
I'm sorry, Jaguar.
But Madrigal has to pay
for what he did to my son.
He will definitely pay for this!
He will not get away with this!
-Papa, I need to talk to you.
-You got one minute.
I've got a pesky kitten to hunt down!
Declaring war with Jaguar
is not gonna be good for you!
You'll be wasting time,
resources, and men!
He must pay for what he did to Arnaldo!
Papa, if there's anyone
who has to pay, it's not Jaguar.
If not the Jaguar…
then who?
[upbeat music playing]
-[Jepoy grunts]
-[Natalie exclaims]
-Who are you?!
-Madrigal!
Sorry, ma'am.
[exhales]
Did the Ardientes do that to you?
Congressman.
Ivy! [giggles]
What a surprise! Please. Please, sit down.
Join me.
So…
how have you been?
Honestly, Congressman?
I'm upset with you.
Why? What did I do?
[exhales]
Why didn't you tell me…
that you already
brought Arnaldo back home?
Well, let me apologize. I'm sorry.
But I was thinking,
I know you're a busy woman.
Besides, I don't want Arnaldo
to be disturbed for now.
Let him have a couple of days to rest
before he starts accepting visitors, okay?
You don't want Arnaldo to be disturbed?
Why? I'm not a troublemaker. And for sure,
when Arnaldo wakes up,
he'll be happy to see his "hon".
Do you know who the troublemaker is?
Your daughter, Emilia.
[chuckles]
You know, Ivy, you're a bold one.
You know very well that
Emilia is going to raise hell…
if ever she finds out you're here.
I don't care.
And she has no right to stop me
if I want to visit Arnaldo.
Despite all the terrible things
he did to me,
I'm still here for him.
I'm still concerned about him,
and I want to know who shot him.
And I mean, the one who really shot him.
You know, you don't have to wait.
Because we now know who did it.
It's Diego, right?
It was all over the news.
Your camp opened fire at his headquarters.
No, no, no, no. It wasn't Diego.
Sad to say…
I made a mistake. You know, Miss Aguas,
I'm the kind of a man
who admits his mistakes.
And I admit that
I was wrong to suspect Diego,
much as I hate his guts.
Well, since you admitted your mistake,
I assume you feel guilty for all
the other people you've hurt.
Correction, Ivy…
Yes, I admit I made a mistake.
But feel guilty? No.
Why would I?
They deserved every bullet
that flew all over that place!
I tell you, Ivy,
you should've seen their eyes.
The fear in them, when death came calling.
It was priceless!
[Julio chuckling]
Well, whoever your new suspect is…
I hope you finally got the right one.
I don't make mistakes
twice in a row, Miss Aguas.
And I have solid evidence this time.
I'm certain
it was Madrigal who shot Arnaldo.
And
my men are looking for him,
even as we speak.
And I guarantee you…
Madrigal is not getting out of
this situation alive this time.
-So, it's Madrigal?
-Yes.
It's Madrigal.
And he is about to die.
[Jepoy] What's this for?
[man] If you hadn't warned our boss,
we would've gotten into bigger trouble.
[Jepoy] That was nothing, boss.
This is too much.
[Raul] What were you doing
at Mayor Arnaldo's wedding?
I was going to kill Arnaldo,
but I didn't get the chance.
I want to make him feel the
torture they made me go through.
-Leave Mayor Arnaldo to me.
-Why, boss?
Are we supposed to protect him?
[Raul] That's the gun I gave Madrigal.
But I didn't order him to shoot Arnaldo.
He's your henchman,
so he's your responsibility!
Kill him!
[phone ringing]
[Julio] Now, who's calling you?
No one important.
You're so amazing, Congressman.
That's why I look up to you!
Because no one can ever escape
the clutches of…
Julio Ardiente.
[Julio and Ivy chuckling]
I don't think I'm wrong
in saying you already
have a place in hell…
for anyone who gets
in your way or your family's.
Ivy, that's the only way
that you will get two reactions
that are very important in life.
To establish fear
and to get their respect.
Bang,
bang,
bang.
Anyone you don't like? Shoot them down.
Kill them.
If they survive…
well,
good luck to them in the next lifetime
because if I see them again,
I will shoot them down again,
even there.
Well, I have to go, Congressman.
I think I've overstayed my welcome.
Okay. Like I told you,
I know you're a busy woman.
But do be careful.
-You too. Be very careful.
-Thank you.
Ivy?
Yes?
Colonel Sanggano here just informed me
that they already know
where to find Madrigal.
Exactly pinpointed…
at the very location.
Would you like to join me?
Let's go make that bastard suffer.
I like the sound of that, Congressman.
In case you didn't know,
that's one of my favorite activities…
getting payback.
A woman after my own heart. My, my!
[tense music playing]
Auntie, I'm sorry.
The Ardientes were there
because they were after me.
But you got caught in the crossfire.
Diego.
I've accepted the fact that
I have one foot in the grave.
Like everyone else fighting the Ardientes.
What we need to do now…
is stay wary.
Auntie, I promise you that…
I won't let anyone's life
be taken away for the sake of this fight.
[phone ringing]
[Diego] Excuse me.
[ringing continues]
Arthur?
We're almost there.
Ivy.
[phone ringing]
Madrigal.
Boss?
Come with me.
Where are we going, Boss?
Follow us.
[tense music playing]
Divine Uytengco?
Arthur.
Ivy asked me…
to bring her here.
But she won't talk.
You're better at this.
She might listen to you.
[Raul] Did you attempt to
murder Mayor Arnaldo?
I had nothing to do with that, Boss.
Why would I do that?
Besides, the Ardientes are our enemies.
We should be celebrating right now.
-We should be drinking--
-[thuds]
Answer me, Madrigal!
Were you involved?
Boss…
I'm on your side.
Why are you so concerned
about Arnaldo, anyway?
Are you his dad?
You little brat! Talking back now?
[tense music playing]
Sanggano.
Yes, Congressman?
Make sure everything is ready
before Miss Aguas and I enter.
Yes, Congressman.
[tense music playing]
Tell me the truth, Madrigal,
so we can end this once and for all.
And then what? You'll turn me
over to the Ardientes?
I don't understand you! I'm on your side!
What's the problem?
If this is the way my own group
and boss are going to treat me,
then I'll just leave.
Madrigal!
Come back here, Madrigal!
[thuds]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Julio] Surprise! Surprise!
[laughs]
Don't worry, Jaguar.
I am not here…
for the carnage.
If I can avoid it.
[Raul] Congressman.
I thought you were busy with the campaign.
But here you are.
You still have time to visit me.
Put your gun down
if you want me to believe you.
Ivy Aguas.
I think this is our first time
meeting in person.
You truly are a beauty.
May I please kiss your hand?
Don't come near me, Jaguar.
Where is Madrigal?
He was here a while ago.
But now, he's gone.
And, even if he were still here,
I wouldn't just turn him over to you.
Hmm.
You uncouth weasel.
Your man…
used my gun to shoot Arnaldo.
A gun that you stole from my armory.
Now…
for us to settle this nicely,
give me Madrigal.
Or else…
I'll blow this whole place up.
And you know I'm capable of doing that.
[Julio chuckling]
[exhales] Congressman,
I think we already made our point.
It's possible Madrigal
might come back here,
so if you kill Jaguar,
you won't be able to get what you want.
[Julio] You know,
you're such a spoilsport.
Jaguar, you are one lucky man.
So lucky, because we have
a lady in our midst.
Anyway,
I'll give you 24 hours, no more, no less.
Give me Madrigal, or else,
I will book you a one-way ticket to hell,
with Satan as your bodyguard.
[Julio] Oh, well.
[tense music playing]
Until next time.
-[groaning]
-[shushes]
[Arthur] We're good people.
We won't hurt you.
Just cooperate, okay?
[muffled groan]
Here.
Have some water.
Go on.
I said we were good people!
Weren't you listening?!
-Let me go!
-Arthur, it's all right.
I'll talk to her.
Diego Torillo!
The Ardientes' bastard son.
What do you want from me, huh?!
Campaign money?!
Well, you're not going
to get anything from me!
Divine Uytengco, I'll get
straight to the point.
We brought you here to ask you
to be our whistleblower.
We have evidence of your corrupt
activities with Emilia Ardiente.
Is this a joke?
Emilia Ardiente is a friend…
and family!
Well, if you don't cooperate,
you're going to be in big trouble.
And who the hell do you think you are?!
Some ragtag hero for the poor?
Emilia Ardiente is a dear friend,
and she's on my side.
And guess what?
We're not scared of you, or anyone else!
Who do you think you are, anyway?!
Let me go!
I have places to go!
If I get out of here, you'll see!
You'll see!
What do we do now?
-You can't even do this right!
-If I were you…
-I'd use force already.
-What? No.
-Let me go!
-Trust me, Diego.
I used to be a lawyer.
And a case is way
more convincing with a witness.
Arthur, if we force her,
she might just turn on us.
Just be a bit more patient.
[Divine grunting]
We need to get her to talk.
And when we do,
Emilia will go down for sure.
[Divine] I'll have my people
take care of you!
Let's be patient with her.
[Divine] What do you plan to do
to me anyway?!
You can't do this to me.
If you keep resisting, then
you'll never get out of here.
[laughing]
So amateur!
Do you know what you're doing?
Because it sure doesn't look like it!
This is stupid!
[Ivy] Julio will kill you!
And Jaguar wants you dead
because his life is on the line!
Didn't you hear me, Ivy? I'm not leaving!
I'm the one who shot Arnaldo, remember?
So, it should be me!
Jepoy!
-Not you.
-Why?
You think I'll let him live
when he knows all my secrets?!
No way in hell, Jepoy!
I know you, Ivy. You're no murderer.
So, what now?
You'll surrender yourself
to the Ardientes? Really?!
If that's what I have to do, Ivy.
There's no way I'm letting that happen!
Listen to me, Jepoy.
You won't surrender yourself
to the Ardientes.
Enough! We've already gotten
so many people involved in this.
Look at Aunt Camia and the others.
They're all at the hospital!
Fighting is not going to help.
We'll just end up wasting more time!
Diego's right. Let's all talk
about this calmly.
Be on the same page.
I know how you feel, Jepoy.
I know you're more than ready
to turn yourself over.
But it'd be better if we worked
together to bring them down.
Especially Emilia.
Jepoy, please.
Listen to me.
[phone ringing]
Madrigal.
Boss?
That fake Jaguar is becoming…
a real nuisance…
to our group.
Will you really abandon me now,
of all times?
And one more thing, Madrigal.
I apologize…
for what I said earlier.
I didn't mean it.
The group needs you…
and you're the only one I can count on.
Madrigal!
Fine.
I'll do what you want.
I'll keep my distance.
Just make sure you keep your word.
So, are we good?
Luring your prey…
so you can avenge your son?
Or is it because…
you really do need Madrigal?
Who knows? Think of it
however you want, Natalie.
I don't need to explain
myself to you. Got that?
Well,
if I should take a wild guess…
It's for you to protect your son.
Natalie, didn't you come back here…
to avenge your father? Isn't that right?
-Yes.
-Hmm.
-Right.
-But…
unlike you,
my revenge was worth it.
My father loved me.
What about you?
Does your son love you?
Madrigal, on the other hand,
we need him, obviously.
Especially for our next heist.
You know…
we could earn millions from it.
And I'm sure…
it would be enough to compensate
for what Damian took from us.
Do you catch my drift?
We really need Madrigal.
I'll let you decide.
But make sure you choose
the right decision.
Because if not, I'll take
matters into my own hands.
[soft music playing]
Jepoy.
You know, sometimes,
we think someone is meant for us
because we share
something in common with them.
We might think they're our soulmates.
But they aren't.
And that's the truth we need to accept.
Anna.
Listen to me.
I'm leaving this place…
so that you guys won't get
involved in my situation.
Jepoy, didn't Lily tell you to stay here?
Where are you going?
Somewhere far away.
So I can protect you all.
I'll return to the shadows.
[Ivy] You can fight her
because she's just Emilia.
And I am Ivy Aguas.
If you agree to my plans,
Divine, we'll work together,
and we'll bring Emilia down.
Keep an eye on Raul's group.
Find out if they're planning something.
And just like what I did to Emilia,
I will sabotage their plans.
[Raul] This is all your fault!
If not for you, the operation
would have succeeded!
-You did this on purpose, didn't you?!
-No, boss!
Why would I do that?!
What did I ever do to you?
To me? Nothing. But to my son? A lot.
[explosion]
Jepoy.
[theme music playing]